Guide to the Vern Haugland Papers 1908-1987
Maureen and Mike Mansfield Library, The University of Montana--Missoula
- Photographs, 1936-1983 and undated; Series X
  - Group of men standing below Airplane wing, Dallas, Feb. 1965; 153(X)267 (Box 25)
  - V. Haugland and Tess with James Webb, Caller Trophy Award winner, May 1966; 153(X)268 (Box 25)
  - Flight Party aboard de Havilland Twin Otter, La Guardia Airport, New York, May 25 1966; 153(X)269 (Box 25)
  - V. Haugland with other guests at Helicopter Society dinner-dance, May 13 1966; 153(X)270 (Box 25)
  - Ken Fletcher, Bill Hengey, Eric Bromley Gordon Dilmore, Ben Fridge, V. Haugland, Wayne Parrish, Bob Serling, John Corriss, 1967; 153(X)271 (Box 25)
  - Bill Lindsay, Pete Cosgrove, V. Haugland, John Davey, Norfolk, VA, Oct. 1968; 153(X)272 (Box 25)
  - Dr. Joe B. MacJunis and Jon M. Lindbergh, Feb. 17, 1969; 153(X)273 (Box 25)
  - Mr. & Mrs. V. Haugland with Mr. & Mrs. Fred Durant, Nov. 1969; 153(X)274 (Box 25)
  - V. Haugland with Paul Rogers, 1969; 153(X)275 (Box 25)
  - Thomas L. Grace, John Dregge, Whitney Gilland, 1969; 153(X)276 (Box 25)
  - V. Haugland, Dallas, Aug. 1969; 153(X)277 (Box 25)
  - V. Haugland with five unidentified people posing for a picture, Washington, D.C., April 16, 1968; 153(X)278 (Box 25)
  - 1965 Callier Trophy Nominating Committee, June 13, 1966; 153(X)279 (Box 25)
  - Men unloading from DC-9 Flight, April 20, 1966; 153(X)280 (Box 25)
  - Seven unidentified men in suits, Oct. 1968; 153(X)281 (Box 25)
  - V. Haugland with two unidentified men comparing notes, undated; 153(X)282 (Box 25)
  - V. Haugland, Walter Damloft, Neil Obsewer wine tasting at the German Embassy, Washington, Oct. 8, 1970; 153(X)283 (Box 25)
  - Adm. John J. McCain, V. Haugland talking, Pearl Harbor, Honolulu, July 1971; 153(X)284 (Box 25)
  - V. Haugland with many unidentified party guests in suits, Nov. 1970; 153(X)285 (Box 25)
  - Robert Buckhorn, Jerry Hannifin, V. Haugland, Nov. 11, 1970; 153(X)286 (Box 25)
  - Jack Shaffer and other men on TV show set, Nov. 17, 1970; 153(X)287 (Box 25)
  - Sherman Fairchild, V. Haugland, Jerry Hannifin, Nov. 1970; 153(X)288 (Box 25)
  - V. Haugland and other party guests mingling, Nov. 1970; 153(X)289 (Box 25)
  - V. Haugland speaking wit an unidentified man, Transpo Dallas, May 27, 1972; 153(X)290 (Box 25)
  - V. Haugland talking with unidentified men at Transpo, May 27, 1972; 153(X)291 (Box 25)
  - James Beggs, Al Wnerker and their wives, V. Haugland greeting them, Nov. 1972; 153(X)292 (Box 25)
  - V. Haugland with unidentified man at Transpo, Dallas, May 27, 1972; 153(X)293 (Box 25)
  - V. Haugland and unidentified man at Transpo, Dallas, May 27, 1972; 153(X)294 (Box 25)
  - Bob Schulman and Tess at Alpa formal dinner, June 12, 1972; 153(X)295 (Box 25)
  - V. Haugland in the pressroom, 1972; 153(X)296 (Box 25)
  - V. Haugland, Budd Faught, Jerry Banten, Ft. Myer Officer Club, June 1972; 153(X)297 (Box 25)
  - V. Haugland taking notes, April 4, 1973; 153(X)298 (Box 25)
  - V. Haugland receiving a citation, June 26, 1975; 153(X)299 (Box 25)
  - Bob Six and V. Haugland, Los Angeles, June 26, 1975; 153(X)300 (Box 25)
  - Jon Daly, V. & T. Haugland, and two unidentified guests, Los Angeles, June 26, 1975; 153(X)301 (Box 25)
  - V. Haugland receiving the Lauren D. Lyman Memoria Award, Washington, Nov. 9, 1976; 153(X)302 (Box 25)
  - Ralph Cunningham, Bea Wood, Sally Reeve, Betty Coonrad, at Pageant of the Masters, Laguna Beach, CA, undated; 153(X)303 (Box 25)
  - Bert Tarayao, Judi Wetmove, Jean Rolland, Models for Calliers Trohpy, undated; 153(X)304 (Box 25)
  - Sculpture, Laguna Beach Festival of the Arts, undated; 153(X)305 (Box 25)
  - Re-creation of the face of the Congressional Medal of Honor, Pageant of the Masters, July - Aug. 1973; 153(X)306 (Box 25)
  - Ancient Chinese Sculpture, Pageant of the Masters, undated; 153(X)307 (Box 25)
  - Don Williamson, Pagent of the Master's Director, beside Callier Trophy set, undated; 153(X)308 (Box 25)
  - Janet Spurgeon, model, Pageant of the Masters, undated; 153(X)309 (Box 25)
  - The living reproductions, Pageant of the Masters, undated; 153(X)310 (Box 25)
  - Backstage preparations of the Pageant of the Masters, undated; 153(X)311 (Box 25)
  - June and Thurl Ravenscroft sitting on bench, undated; 153(X)312 (Box 25)
  - Thurl Ravenscroft, new narrator of the Pageant of the Masters, undated; 153(X)313 (Box 25)
  - Bronze sculpture, original by Edward Wise Keyser, undated; 153(X)314 (Box 25)
  - Models for Empress and Her Court as Donors await position, Pageant of the Masters, undated; 153(X)315 (Box 25)
  - Pageant of the Masters recreation of Norman Rockwell's 1969 Moon landing, 1971; 153(X)316 (Box 25)
  - Rockwell's painting of 1969 Moon Landing, 1971; 153(X)317 (Box 25)
  - Recreation of Rockwell's "The Longest Step," Pageant of the Masters, 1969; 153(X)318 (Box 25)
  - Models for "The Longest Step" receive wardrobe checks, 1969; 153(X)319 (Box 25)
  - Print of Original Rockwell painting "The Longest Step;" undated, 153(X)320 (Box 25)
  - Model of Vanguard I, NASA photo, March 17, 1960; 153(X)321 (Box 25)
  - Three men in NASA jumpsuits, one in navel uniform, undated; 153(X)322 (Box 25)
  - Man in NASA jumpsuit in front of helicopter, undated; 153(X)323 (Box 25)
  - Man in west suit with flippers jumping into the water, undated; 153(X)324 (Box 25)
  - Apollo 9 crew aboard the U.S.S. Guadacanal, March 13, 1969; 153(X)325 (Box 25)
  - Apollo 9 spacecraft in orbit around the moon viewing earth, undated; 153(X)326 (Box 25)
  - Drawing of docking of U.S. Apollo and U.S.S.R. Soyuz, 1975; 153(X)327 (Box 25)
  - Skylab 4 Recovery aboard U.S.S. New Orleans, 1974; 153(X)328 (Box 25)
  - Dr. Edward G. Gibson, Skylab 4 pilot, emerging from from the spacecraft, Feb 8, 1974; 153(X)329 (Box 25)
  - Crew relaxing after Skylab 4 splashdown, Feb. 8, 1974; 153(X)330 (Box 25)
  - Edward G. Gibson sitting and smiling between medical examinations, Feb 8, 1974; 153(X)331 (Box 25)
  - Arial view of Northeast Wyoming from skylab, 1974; 153(X)332 (Box 25)
  - Skylab 4 astronaut with their wives, Ellington AFB, Huston, Feb. 14, 1974; 153(X)333 (Box 25)
  - Three parachutes above ocean during splashdown, undated; 153(X)334 (Box 25)
  - Helicopter with men being pulled up, spacecraft to the left, undated; 153(X)335 (Box 25)
  - Spacecraft in ocean, undated; 153(X)336 (Box 25)
  - Spacecraft being lowered onto aircraft carrier, undated; 153(X)337 (Box 25)
  - Apollo 9 recovery, crew member hanging from helicopter, U.S.S. Guadalcanal in background, March 13, 1969; 153(X)338 (Box 25)
  - Crewmembers of Apollo 10, undated; 153(X)339 (Box 25)
  - Apollo 9 crewmembers, undated; 153(X)340 (Box 25)
  - Launch of Saturn-Apollo (SA-6), May 28, 1964; 153(X)341 (Box 25)
  - Gemini 3 Astronauts, Back-up crew, undated; 153(X)342 (Box 25)
  - Friendship 7 cake for celebration of first manned American orbit, undated; 153(X)343 (Box 25)
  - Apollo 11 crew, undated; 153(X)344 (Box 25)
  - Sally K. Ride - Autographed, undated; 153(X)345 (Box 25)
  - V. Haugland at Heathrow Airport, London, Concord in background, Jan. 21, 1976; 153(X)346 (Box 25)
  - Three unidentified men in pilots uniforms, Jan. 21, 1976; 153(X)347 (Box 25)
  - Concord in flight, undated; 153(X)348 (Box 25)
  - Concord taking off for first commercial flight, Jan. 21, 1976; 153(X)349 (Box 25)
  - Concord being loaded at Heathrow Airport, London, Jan. 21, 1976; 153(X)350 (Box 25)
  - Brian Calvert, Concord Captain, 1976; 153(X)351 (Box 25)
  - Alan Beaves, Concorde Marketing Manager, undated; 153(X)352 (Box 25)
  - Icebergs off Greenland, with Greenland faintly in the distance, undated; 153(X)353 (Box 25)
  - Godthaab, Greenland, undated; 153(X)354 (Box 25)
  - V. Haugland with three girls and unidentified man, Greenland, undated; 153(X)355 (Box 25)
  - V. Haugland with unidentified group in front of Royal Danish Airforce plane, undated; 153(X)356 (Box 25)
  - V. Haugland in Thule, Greenland, undated; 153(X)357 (Box 25)
  - Unidentified man saddling a horse in a pen, undated; 153(X)358 (Box 25)
  - Group of men in front of 121 Dispersal Hut, March 1942; 153(X)359 (Box 25)
  - VTO Press crew leaving Burbank, CA, Nov. 6, 1954; 153(X)360 (Box 25)
  - Unidentified group of men, aboard U.S.S. Intrepid CVA-11, undated; 153(X)361 (Box 25)
  - V. Haugland with unidentified man by helicopter, undated; 153(X)362 (Box 25)
  - V. Haugland looking at shorter man, undated; 153(X)363 (Box 25)
  - Baron Francis Fiorio, Gen. Maurie Casey, V. Haugland, Bill Boyle, undated; 153(X)364 (Box 25)
  - V. Haugland at dinner table with other men, undated; 153(X)365 (Box 25)
  - V. Haugland talking with unidentified man, both wearing suits, undated; 153(X)366 (Box 25)
  - V. Haugland receiving papers from unidentified woman and man, undated; 153(X)367 (Box 25)
  - Military cartoon by Capt. R.G. Leffingwell, New Delhi, India; March, 1944; 153(X)368 (Box 25)
  - Coastline with palm trees, roads, and buildings and a long dock, undated; 153(X)369 (Box 25)
  - Map of unidentified Launch Pad, undated; 153(X)370 (Box 25)
  - Map of typical telemetry site, undated; 153(X)371 (Box 25)
  - Map of globe showing there sites of Ballistici Missile Early Warnning System and their global coverage, with info sheet, undated; 153(X)372 (Box 25)
  - Group of men aboard the U.S.S. Valley Forge, with transparency, Jan. 1960; 153(X)373 (Box 25)
  - Three unidentified men, two stepping towards each other, undated; 153(X)374 (Box 25)
  - Five unidentified men standing and sitting near ocean, one operating NBC camera, undated; 153(X)375 (Box 25)
  - Long row of cameras with operators on top of a building, undated; 153(X)376 (Box 25)
  - Unidentified group of journalists and others on bleachers, undated; 153(X)377 (Box 25)
  - Three unidentified men using wooden phone booths, one man squatting nearby, undated; 153(X)378 (Box 25)
  - Row of camera men on top of building, undated; 153(X)379 (Box 25)
  - Andraus Building engulfed in blames, Brazil, undated; 153(X)380 (Box 25)
  - Native on a donkey in front of the Suq-Al-Khamis Mosque, Bahrain, undated; 153(X)381 (Box 25)
  - Unidentified group of men chatting outside a building, undated; 153(X)382 (Box 25)
  - Unidentified group infront of plane, undated; 153(X)383 (Box 25)
  - Four unidentified men in a circle, one holding a circuit board, undated; 153(X)384 (Box 25)
  - E.C. Alsenz, president of unnamed entity, working with a dark machine with button and dials, undated; 153(X)385 (Box 25)
  - Sign "Eagle Way", Martlesham Heath, Suffok, undated; 153(X)386 (Box 25)
  - WWII Memorial Plaque, Martlesham Heath, Suffolk, undated; 153(X)387 (Box 25)
  - World Congress Flight, Las Vegas, NV, undated; 153(X)388 (Box 25)
  - Three slides of the Concord, two copies of each, undated; 153(X)389 (Box 25)
  - Slide of military plane, undated; 153(X)390 (Box 25)
  - Slide of military plane, undated; 153(X)391 (Box 25)
  - Slide of V. Haugland in cage going down zipline, undated; 153(X)392 (Box 25)
  - Slide of V. Haugland, Canaveral Trip, undated; 153(X)393 (Box 25)
  - Slide of V. Haugland, Canaveral Trip, undated; 153(X)394 (Box 25)
  - McDonnell Aircraft F2H-2P photo, Banshee, 153(X)395 (Box OS 1/4)
  - McDonnell Aircraft F2H-3 photo, All-weather Banshee, 153(X)396 (Box OS 1/4)
  - Young V. Haugland in suit, undated; 153(X)397 (Box OS 1/5)
  - V. Haugland with Lucille Ball, 153(X)398 (Box OS 1/6)
  - V. Haugland in a group of unidentified Chinese men, Weh-sein, Northern China, 1945; 153(X)399 (Box OS 1/7)
  - V. Haugland with Airline personnel in background, possibly 707 press flight, undated; 153(X)400 (Box 25)
  - Unidentified man explaining United's DC-8 Jet Mainliner, undated; 153(X)401 (Box 25)
  - U.S. Navy Helicopter Responding to Apollo 17 capsule sea landing, 1972; 153(X)402; oversize photograph (Box OS 1/8)
  - Apollo 11 Lift-off, 1969; 153(X)403; oversize photograph (Box 25)
- Lithographs, undated; Series XI
  This series includes twelve aircraft lithographs presented to Haugland as a gift from Northrop Aircraft Inc. at an unknown date.
  - Set of twelve aircraft lithographs (Box-folder OS 1/9)